<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>In Tenant Struggle on</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/</link><description>Recent content in In Tenant Struggle on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ETOC</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc/</guid><description>ETOC stands for Emergency Tenant Organizing Committee. The purpose of ETOC is to create new autonomous tenant unions.
ETOC is part of the Housing Justice Commision (HJC), which is part of DSA.</description></item><item><title>ETOC Curriculum</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc-curriculum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc-curriculum/</guid><description>ETOC’s Mentorship Program has 5 Phases.
Phase 1: Pre-configuration – consolidate working &amp;amp; process norms such as recurring meetings, socials, and how to onboard new members Phase 2: Inquiry – review popular outreach approaches, frame organizing convos that involve the law, and canvas as a tenant in your block or building Phase 3: TU Skeleton – minimal operations as a dues-collecting member organization with a public purpose and outward-facing materials Phase 4: Fight – conduct pressure campaigns against landlords as a mass organization where tenants lead their own struggle and not as a service org Phase 5: TU Formation – formalize decision-making procedures, define political line that unites multiple tendencies, and streamline procedures to enable new member involvement as TU grows</description></item><item><title>Journey to Mentorship</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc-entrypoints/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/etoc-entrypoints/</guid><description>As long as you have 3+ core TU organizers and some observable commitment to building an ATU, then we let any group join ETOC Mentorship.</description></item><item><title>My ATU and ETOC</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/atus-x-etoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/atus-x-etoc/</guid><description>So your ATU is/was part of ETOC’s Mentorship Program. What does this mean?
Your ATU is connected to the larger tenants movement.</description></item><item><title>Why ETOC</title><link>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/why-join-etoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://intenantstruggle.github.io/notes/notes/why-join-etoc/</guid><description>People have said nice things about their ETOC experience.
The ETOC 2 Day Training is really good. After we first got trained we sent people who had missed it to subsequent trainings.</description></item></channel></rss>